{"test_questions": [[{"question": "Which of the following statements is true about symmetric multiprocessing?", "opta": "A single copy of the operating system resides in each processor.", "optb": "Useful for situations where data must remain in memory to process.", "optc": "Bottlenecks increase with uniprocessor systems because tasks are not shared.", "optd": "The problems of memory contention are unlikely.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following items are not necessary for client/server?", "opta": "Assure that tools will connect with middleware.", "optb": "Understand the requirements.", "optc": "Determine network bandwidth capabilities.", "optd": "Include the use of a file server.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A benefit of the three-tier architecture is which of the following?", "opta": "New modules can be built to support specific business needs", "optb": "Performance improves for compiled SQL statements", "optc": "Results in a thinner client and database server", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following statements is true concerning JDBC?", "opta": "It is language independent.", "optb": "It is similar in concept to ODBC.", "optc": "It is useful for all object-oriented languages.", "optd": "It consists of three main layers.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A characteristic of a file server is which of the following?", "opta": "Manages file operations and is shared on a network.", "optb": "Manages file operations and is limited to one PC.", "optc": "Acts as a fat client and is shared on a network.", "optd": "Acts as a fat client and is limited to one PC.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Stored procedures have which of the following advantages?", "opta": "It takes a longer time to write them as compared to writing Visual Basic.", "optb": "Network traffic increases", "optc": "Data integrity improves as multiple applications access the same stored procedure.", "optd": "Result in thicker client and thinner database server.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following statements is a true statement concerning the open database connectivity standard (ODBC)?", "opta": "Each vendor desiring to be ODBC-complaint provides an ODBC driver.", "optb": "Requires certain criteria to be met in order to establish an ODBC connection.", "optc": "Provides a programming interface that provides a common language for application programs to access and process SQL databases independent of the RDBMS accessed.", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is true concerning QBE?", "opta": "An official standard has been defined for QBE.", "optb": "QBE cannot be used for client/server systems.", "optc": "QBE does not give the programmer a visual programming environment.", "optd": "Complete applications can be written using QBE.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Client/server security includes which of the following?", "opta": "Physical security", "optb": "Change control security", "optc": "Measures taken to secure all systems", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "An application program interface (API) is which of the following?", "opta": "The same thing as ODBC.", "optb": "Middleware that does not provide access to a database.", "optc": "Middleware that provides access to a database.", "optd": "The same thing as JDBC.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Three-tier architecture includes which of the following?", "opta": "Three server layers", "optb": "A client layer and two server layers", "optc": "Two client layers and one server layer", "optd": "Three client layers", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is true concerning the mainframe?", "opta": "It is the same thing as client/server.", "optb": "Requires someone to decide which code should be on the workstation or the server.", "optc": "Mission-critical systems have tended to remain there.", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A server cannot serve on which of the following levels?", "opta": "Client Layer", "optb": "Business Layer", "optc": "Database Layer", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The three different application logic components are which of the following?", "opta": "Presentation, Client, and Storage", "optb": "Presentation, Client, and Processing", "optc": "Presentation, Processing, and Storage", "optd": "Presentation, Processing, and Network", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A database server is responsible for which of the following?", "opta": "Database storage", "optb": "Data processing logic", "optc": "Data presentation logic", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}